quiksee.com 2008-09-17

# 

Welcome to the Web site of QuikseeTM (the ”Web site” and the “Company” respectively). 

The Company takes the privacy of your personal information very seriously and will use your information given and/or collected on the Web site only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”). The Company will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our Web site Users to third parties. However, as more detailed below, there are limited circumstances in which some of your information will be shared with third parties, under strict restrictions, so it is important for you to review this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all services that are hosted on the Web site, whether the services offered by the Company, by its subsidiaries, or by any other third party enterprises.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Web site’s terms of use (the “Terms”) as published by the Company at the bottom of the home page of Web site, Therefore by accessing, browsing and/or using this Web site and its contents you agree and consent to the terms of this privacy policy. 

Please note that your personal information will be stored and processed on our computers in Israel. The laws on holding personal data in Israel may be less stringent than the laws of your country but the Company will hold and transmit your personal information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. If you object to your personal information being transferred or used as described in this Privacy Policy, please do not register for the different services offered and provided on the Web site. 

Notification of Changes

The Company reserves the right at its sole discretion to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please check the Company’s Web site at any time for the most current version of our Privacy Policy in order to review what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. 

The Web site includes links to third party Web sites, these Web sites are governed by their own privacy statements, and the Company is not responsible for their operations, including but not limited to their information practices. Users submitting information to or through these third party Web sites should review the privacy statement of these sites before providing them with personally identifiable information.

Information We Collect

Requested Information

To register for the different services provided on the Web site, you may be requested to provide your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address. We also may ask you to choose two different security questions to answer (such as your city of birth or your pet’s name) This required information is necessary for us to issue a new password if you forget or lose your password, protect you against frauds, and to contact you should the need arise.

Supplemental Information

Some services on the Web site may require you to provide additional information other than the aforesaid information (the “Supplemental Information”). The Supplemental Information is required since the Web site offers and provides unique services for business users of the Company that are restricted for other users. 

Our Use of "Cookies"

"Cookies" are small files of data that reside on your computer and allow us to recognize you as a user of the Company’s Web site if you return to the Web site using the same computer and browser. We send a "session cookie" to your computer if and when you log in to your Web site account (the “Web Account”) by entering your e-mail address and password. These cookies allow us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages in our site during the same session, so that you don’t need to re-enter your password multiple times. Once you log out or close your browser, these session cookies expire and no longer have any effect. 

We also use longer-lasting cookies to display your e-mail address on our sign-in form, so that you don’t have to retype the e-mail address each time when you log in to your Web Account. We may share cookie information regarding whether or not a certain user is already registered with the Company’s Web site with certain enterprises with whom we have an official relationship.

Our Use and Disclosure of Information 

Internal Uses

We collect, store and process your personal information on servers located in Israel. We use the information we collect about you in order to: (A) provide our services; (B) provide restrict business services; (C) determine your eligibility to receive offers for special features or products; and (D) improve our products and services. 

We give access to individually identifiable information about our users only to the Company’s employees who require it to fulfill customer service.

Disclosure to Third Parties

We work with third party enterprises that provide different kinds of content and services on the Web site and therefore we enable them to view your personally identifiable information. Any additional information provided by you to these third party enterprises is subject to their own private policies and is not under any responsibility of the Company. 

We may disclose the information we collect to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf. We may also disclose the information we collect to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. These companies are restricted by law and are prohibited to use the information except to market the specified products or services that are offered on the Web site, unless you have affirmatively agreed or given your prior permission for other uses. 

We disclose information in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, levy, attachment, order of a court-appointed receiver or other comparable legal process. We disclose information to your agent or legal representative (such as the holder of a power of attorney that you grant, or a guardian appointed for you). We share aggregated statistical data with our business partners or for public relations. For example, we may disclose that a specific percentage of our users live in the city of Haifa, Israel. However, this aggregated information is not tied to personally identifiable information. 

Our Contacts with our Web site Users

We communicate with our Web site users via e-mail to provide requested services. We use your e-mail address to confirm your Web Account opening, to send you business proposals and notices, to send information about important changes to our products and services, to send you third-party promotions and to send notices and other disclosures required by law. 

You can choose whether to receive some, all or none of these communications when you complete the registration process, or at any time thereafter, by logging in to your account on the Company’s Web site and changing your preferences.

Internet Address Information

We use IP addresses, browser types and access times to analyze trends, administer the Web site, improve site performance and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

The Company does not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you may not add a 

Company’s Web site user to your mail list (email or physical mail) without their express consent after adequate disclosure.

Information Security

The Company is committed to handling your information with high standards of information security. Your Web Account information is stored only in encrypted form on computers that are not connected to the Internet. We restrict access to your personally identifiable information to employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. 

The security of your Web Account also relies on your protection of your Web Account password. You may not share your password with anyone. The Company will never ask you to send your password or other sensitive information to us in an e-mail, though we may ask you to enter this type of information on the Web site. 

If you do share your Web Account password with a third party for any reason, including because the third-party has promised to provide you additional services, the third party will have access to your account and your personal information, and you may be responsible for actions taken using your password. If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password, please change it immediately by logging in to your Web Account and changing your profile settings.

Accessing and Changing Your Information

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to such information, or to the settings for your Web Account, at any time by logging in to your Web Account on the Web site and changing your preferences. You can also close your Web Account through the Web site. If you close your Web Account, we will mark your account in our database as "Closed," but will keep your account information in our database. If you close your account, your personally identifiable information will not be used by us for any further purposes, nor sold or shared with third parties, except as necessary.

|
